https://anatol.com/privacy-policy/

+1(847) 367-9760info@anatol.com
enruplfres HomeAboutEventsCustomer StoriesAnatol TVAnatol EbooksVacanciesEquipmentPressesConveyor DryersFlash Cure UnitsPre-PressScreen Printing AccessoriesCompare PressesROI CalculatorWhere to buy/QuoteDirect SalesDealersCustomer StoriesFinancingSupportParts StoreBlogContact0ruplfresen Anatol \ Privacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyPrivacy PolicyAt Anatol Equipment Manufacturing Co, we respect your privacy and are committed to keeping your contact information confidential. To that end, Anatol has established strict privacy guidelines and practices to ensure that your private information remains safe, and we offer this Privacy Policy for your assurance. We WILL NOT SELL, TRADE, RENT, or GIVE your personal information to third parties. Registration on our website is voluntary and for the purpose of providing customers with requested product and/or company information. Because we value your trust, we provide this statement to inform our users of how we gather and utilize personal information.Collection and use of informationWhen you register on the Anatol website, we ask you for very limited contact information, which we store in a database on our server. We use this information to process your requests for additional information, and to communicate with you about the status of your inquiry. If you have asked to receive newsletters and/or special offers and promotional announcements, we use your email address to deliver them to you.Viewing and updating your information with usYou can always change the information you have provided to Anatol by logging in to “Your Account” and clicking on “View/Update Your Account Profile.” You can also use this page to change your account password.If you no longer wish to receive an Anatol Newsletter or other notification, please modify your preferences by logging in to “Your Account” and clicking on “Manage Your Email Subscriptions,” then deselecting the appropriate checkboxes.CookiesAs you browse the Anatol site, we place cookies on your computer’s hard drive. (Cookies are small pieces of data that are sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your hard drive.) Cookies allow us to track sessions and personalize your experience on our site. Such uses allow us to improve our site and better tailor it to meet our users’ needs. Anatol will not share your information with anyone who is not an employee or affiliate of Anatol Equipment Manufacturing Co.If your browser is NOT set to accept cookies, you will still be able to use the Anatol site and services. However, our server will not recognize you, and you may have to retype your contact information to request newsletters or equipment information.DisclosureAnatol will not sell, trade, rent, or give your personal information to third parties. We never provide anyone with customer information collected from our website. Registration on our website is voluntary and for the purpose of providing customers with requested product and/or company information. Internally, we may use this information to customize your experience on the Anatol site, to analyze site usage, and to improve our content and product offerings.From time to time, we may partner with companies whose products we believe will interest our users. In conjunction with these partners, we occasionally send joint promotional announcements to our registered customers. However, we do not provide your name or contact information to our marketing partners. We may use a vendor to carry out these mailings, but the partner company never sees your email address or any other information that could identify you or be used to contact you directly. No exceptions to this policy will be made without your permission.Customers should check back for updates to this policy. However, Anatol will not use your information in a manner different from that stated when you registered without first obtaining your consent.ContactIf you have questions concerning your registration information or this privacy policy, please contact us. Search Search for:
Recent articlesTypes of fleece: advantages & disadvantagesThere’s still a ...How to Use Post-Exposure to Create Durable Screen Printing StencilsEvery screen ...CategoriesSCREEN PRINTING (184)SCREEN PRINTING BUSINESS (145)SCREEN PRINTING CONVEYOR DRYERS (5)SCREEN PRINTING EQUIPMENT (11)SCREEN PRINTING EXPOSURE UNITS (8)SCREEN PRINTING FLASH CURES (7)SCREEN PRINTING PRE-PRESS (11)SCREEN PRINTING PRESSES (32)SCREEN PRINTING SUPPLIES (48)SCREEN PRINTING TECHNIQUES (76)Tagsautomatic press automatic screen printing press digital marketing DTG printing electric automatic press exposure unit heat transfer printing manual screen printing press marketing print screen screen printing screen printing accessories screen printing apparel screen printing artwork screen printing business screen printing customers screen printing design screen printing emulsion screen printing equipment screen printing equipment setup screen printing exposure screen printing exposure unit screen printing industry screen printing ink screen printing inks screen printing machine screen printing machines screen printing marketing screen printing methods screen printing pallets screen printing prepress screen printing press screen printing pricing screen printing products screen printing reclamation screen printing screens screen printing shirts screen printing squeegees screen printing stencil screen printing stencils screen printing supplies screen printing techniques screen printing troubleshooting serigrafia serigraficaRegional OfficesAnatol Equipment Manufacturing Co.World Headquarters919 Sherwood Drive Lake Bluff, IL 60044, USAPhone: 847-367-9760Service: 847-582-1825Fax: 847-582-1854sales@anatol.comAnatol EuropeEuropean HeadquartersUl Rejonowa 10 17-100 Bielsk Podlaski, PolandPhone: (+48) 85 731 93 00Fax: (+48)
85 730 1779internationalsales@anatol.comAnatol UkraineEuropean OfficeSmilyvykh Street, 28A, Lviv, UkrainePhone: +38 063 989 26 77Fax: 847-582-1854internationalsales@anatol.comAnatol Latin AmericaLatin American OfficeSan Salvador El SalvadorPhone: 847-604-3223Fax: 847-582-1854internationalsales@anatol.comVisit UsAnatol Equipment Manufacturing Co. 919 Sherwood Drive Lake Bluff, IL 60044 Phone: 847.367.9760 E-mail: info@anatol.comSalesPhone: 847.367.9760 Fax: 847.582.1854 Visit our sales page E-mail: sales@anatol.comServiceFor service request related information, please contact our service support or email us at service@anatol.comInfoAboutCareersTerms of useReturn and Refund PolicyPrivacy Policy0Follow us
Copyright © 2018-2020 Anatol Equipment Manufacturing Co. All Rights Reserved.
Get a Quote
First Name*
Last Name*
Company Name
Phone Number*
Email*
Country Select Country*United StatesUnited KingdomAfghanistanAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos (Keeling) IslandsColombiaComorosCongoCongo, The Democratic Republic of TheCook IslandsCosta RicaCote D'ivoireCroatiaCubaCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEthiopiaFalkland Islands (Malvinas)Faroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuineaGuinea-bissauGuyanaHaitiHeard Island and Mcdonald IslandsHoly See (Vatican City State)HondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIran, Islamic Republic ofIraqIrelandIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKorea, Democratic People's Republic ofKorea, Republic ofKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyan Arab JamahiriyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacaoNorth MacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesia, Federated States ofMoldova, Republic ofMonacoMongoliaMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNetherlands AntillesNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestinian Territory, OccupiedPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarReunionRomaniaRussian FederationRwandaSaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and The GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbia and MontenegroSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth Georgia and The South Sandwich IslandsSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan MayenSwazilandSwedenSwitzerlandSyrian Arab RepublicTaiwan, Province of ChinaTajikistanTanzania, United Republic ofThailandTimor-lesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUnited States Minor Outlying IslandsUruguayUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaViet NamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
State/Region* Please Select State/Region*AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaPuerto RicoRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingAlbertaBritish ColumbiaManitobaNew BrunswickNewfoundland and LabradorNorthwest TerritoriesNova ScotiaNunavutOntarioPrince Edward IslandQuebecSaskatchewanYukon Territories
What equipment are you interested in?
Additional Info
